有一次我不得不撬开后备箱逃走
I once had to chew my way out of the trunk of a car.
你以为你有麻烦了
You think you've got problems?
我的麻烦多到数不清  斯坦福
I've got a mullet, Stanford.
与此同时  你又在哪里呢
Meanwhile, where have you been?
你在树林中漂亮的小屋里快活
Living it up in your fancy house in the woods,
自私地屯着你大学的学费
selfishly hoarding your college money,
因为你只在乎你自己
because you only care about yourself.
我自私吗  我自私吗
I'm selfish? I'm selfish?
斯坦利  你怎么能这么说
Stanley, how can you say that
是你让我梦想中的大学化作泡影
after costing me my dream school?
我在给你机会  让你做一件你生命中最有价值的事情
I'm giving you a chance to do the first worthwhile thing in your life,
可你连听都不听
and you won't even listen.
那你听我说
Well, listen to this.
你想让我丢掉这本书
You want me to get rid of this book?
好啊  我现在就让它彻底不见
Fine, I'll get rid of it right now.
不  你不明白
No! You don't understand.
你说你想让我保管它
You said you wanted me to have it,